# Ehab Mohamed ElSayed Terra

Senior Software developer and Al Engineer

Born 1984 in Yemen





## Experience

#### Senior Developer

Freelancing since April 2020

Using Golang and Elasticsearch to build insight website. Also, involved in other projects using C#, Angular 8, NodeJS, Typescript and ElectronJS.

## Senior Software Developer

Ignite (Remote - Netherlands)

October 2016 - December 2019

Build new features and maintenance websites, services and tools for job vacancies websites in Netherlands and other countries.

#### Senior Software Developer

Comex

October 2014 - October 2016

Responsible for building a web application for reporting, sales, purchases, warehouses, and real estate.

## Senior Software Developer

Hindawi

November 2012 - October 2014

Responsible for Back office website for publishing books and articles.

#### Senior Software Developer

MENA Software (Remote - Bulgaria)

February 2012 - November 2012

Developing Games Portals, Administrations and Gates websites.

#### Developer

TeBAS, True Technology

2004 - 2009

Developed a web and desktop applications for Personnel (HR, Time Attendance, Payroll), Hospital, POS and Restaurant.



## Education

Master of Computer Science

October 2014 - November 2020

Major in Text Clustering and Data Mining, Cairo University.

**Higher Diploma** 

2009 - 2011

Major in Computer Science, Cairo University.

**Bachelor of Commerce** 

2002 - 2006

Major in Accounting, Ain Shams University.

# <>> Projects

### best-resume-ever

Vue

🕆 🖴 Build fast 🖋 and easy multiple beautiful resumes and create your best CV ever! Made with Vue and LESS.



#### About me

I have more than 12 years of experience in software development, I involved in the full-stack development of web applications using C#, NodeJs, Golang,...etc for the back-end and AngularJS for the front-end. Beside that, I was publishing researches in the topics of text clustering and feature selection mainly using R as a part of the Master Degree.

Also proficient in SQL Server, Angular 8, Latex, and Docker, grew up bilingual (Arabic and English).

## Skills

R language

Python, Numpy, Pandas, matplotlib,

Apache Spark

Hadoop

Elastic search

HTML, CSS3 and JavaScript

Node.js and TypeScript

Golang

C#

## Contact

3rd district 4th Area

ehabterra@hotmail.com

+20 106 122 7558

https://www.linkedin.com/in/ehabterra-271b3a23/

ehabterra